{"data":[{"question":"Ann hoped ________ to join the private club. She could make important business contracts there.","a":"inviting","b":"being invited","c":"to invite","d":"to be invited","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Hope to verb- passive voice: hope to be +pp.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The fact that many students tend ________ interest in literature.","a":"lose","b":"losing","c":"to lose","d":"being lost","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tend to Verb: if something tends to happen, it happens often and is likely to happen again.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The tourists complained ________ any sleep.","a":"for not getting","b":"about not getting","c":"on not getting","d":"in not getting","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Complain about sth\/(not) doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"She's perfectly ________ in her demands.","a":"reason","b":"reasoned","c":"reasonable","d":"reasonably","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adverbs go before adjectives they modify","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"It is a thing worth ________.","a":"being done","b":"to be done","c":"doing","d":"do","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be worth doing sth: good enough for doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"There are ways ________ that.","a":"doing","b":"to be done","c":"done","d":"to do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Way to do something: a method of doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Prices continue to show an upward ________.","a":"tend","b":"tendency","c":"tendentious","d":"tendentiously","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A\/an + adj + noun (noun phrase).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The quality of this photograph is not noticeably different ________ that one.","a":"for","b":"with","c":"from","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be different from something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"You should get into the habit of ________ at least one newspaper daily.","a":"to read","b":"reading","c":"being read","d":"read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Habit of doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"It is very important that you learn how ________ this tool.","a":"to use","b":"using","c":"use","d":"used","answer":"1","explain":"\n- How to do something: used for asking about the method of doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}